CURRICULUM VITAE

Mr. Dhrumil Jayeshbhai Upadhyaya

B - 106 Saujanya Tenaments, Nr. Parasnagar, Isanpur,

Vatva Road, Ahmedabad.-382443

MOBILE: 94284 19959

E-MAIL: dhrumil_upadhyay@ymail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVES

To work with a progressive organization, in which I can contributes my background knowledge, skills and experience which I have gained, at the same time achieving the organizational objectives with the attributes of time, quality and discipline.

EDUCATION

2009 - 2010

LONDON SCHOOL OF ACCOUNTANCY AND MANAGEMENT, LONDON - (EDEXCEL) POST GRADUATE DIPLOMA MANAGEMENT STUDIES

2003 - 2007

SYMBIOSIS CENTRE FOR DISTANCE LEARNING (SCDL), Pune
POST GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (PGDBA)

2000-2003

GUJARAT UNIVERSITY

Gujarat University, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India.

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

1998 - 2000

GUJARAT SECONDARY AND HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD

Sector 10, near old Sachivalaya, Gandhinagar-382043 (INDIA)

STANDARD - 10+2 (H.S.C)

1997 - 1998

GUJARAT SECONDARY AND HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD

Sector 10, near old Sachivalaya, Gandhinagar-382043 (INDIA)

STANDARD - 10 (S.S.C)

WORK EXPERIENCE

GUJARAT FOUNDARIES (Oct 2018 to Continue)

HR Assistant

• H.R. Functions

- o Co-ordination with all departments,
- o Joining formalities,
- o Preparation of **full and final settlement** statements.
- Maintain H.R. related records on monthly / yearly basis i.e. Employee Data Base, Leave Records for Regular / Contractor employees, Increment Detail, and Leave without pay records etc.

• Salary Administration Functions

- o Preparation and maintain of Salary, Wages, Over-Time and Leave Register.
- o Preparation of Quarterly Return of L.W.F.
- o Preparation of C.T.C. (Month Wise and Department Wise).
- o Preparation of Bonus Register (Form-C).

• Industrial Relation Functions:-

- Grievance handling, Domestic enquiries, Welfare of employees, Statutory / Non statutory compliances under various acts like: E.P.F., E.S.I., L.W.F. Factory Act etc.
- o Insurance like Accident Policy, CAR & Transport related.
- Liasioning with Government Authorities like P.F., E.S.I., Health and Safety, Pollution, Fire, Red-Cross, Police and Transport etc.

• Administrative Functions

- Ensuring repair and maintenance of Building, Gen. Set and office equipments like Photostat machine, Fax machine, Fans & Air Conditioners and other assets.
- o Controlling system of House Keeping, Security, Pantry and Transport etc.

DIAMOND TEXTILE MILLS PVT, LTD (Jan 2018 to Oct 2018)

HR Assistant

- Manpower Planning.
- Recruitment & Selection.
- Joining Formalities.
- All types of office Latter Like- Offer Letter, Appointment letter, Experience Letter, Relieving Letter, Increment Letter, Promotion/Demotion Letter, Warning Letter, absenteeism notice, Termination Letter Show Cause Notice, Circular etc.
- Induction Training.
- Statutory & Legal Compliance.

- Grievance Handling.
- Performance Appraisal.
- Employee Track Records (Personnel file maintaining).
- Overall Payroll Process using attendance system.
- Salary, Attendance, Leave, Bonus, Overtime, OD, PF, Advance Salary and other calculations.
- Employee Welfare & Engagement activities.
- Conducting Exit Interviews.
- Full & Final Settlements of employees.

SHYAMA SHYAM VSK BUS OPERATION PVT. LTD. (July 2012 to NOV 2017)

(Ahmedabad Municipal Transport Service - OPERATOR)

Store Supervisor

- Preparing PO's, Ordering Materials, receiving & checking
- Arranging of Materials.
- Communicating to the manager for stock.
- Issuing and Receiving of Material on daily basis to Mechanic Staff.
- Assisting Mechanic and Helper for preparing job card related work.
- All stock entry should be entered in to Company's software.
- Assisting to the Depot Manager their work shop related query.

VADH ENTERPRISE (May 2011 to June 2012)

Administration Assistant

Responsibility:

- To help for recruitment and selection of sales staff.
- To co-ordination with sales manager to improve the sales.
- To prepare MIS reports of sales and stock.
- I have to issue and generate the bill for the customer
- Travel and Transport co-ordination

VADH ENTERPRISE (Feb 2005 to June 2009)

Administration Assistant

Responsibility:

- I have to make MIS reports of sales and stock.
- I have to issue and generate the bill for the customer
- Travel and Transport co-ordination
- Prepare Monthly expenditure report for the administrative and facilities cost

- I have to make plan for the sales report for the month on month.
- Maintain the office stationary, housekeeping material, and pantry iteams.
- I have to issue purchase order.
- I have to manage and organize the training program for the sales people.
- I have to take attendance and maintain that register.
- I have to report to manager

YUG INDUSTRIES (June 2003 to Jan 2005)

Computer Operator

Responsibility

- I have to put all the data in safe.
- Provide the data on requirement

SKILLS

PERSONAL SKILL	PROFESSIONAL SKILL
Analyzing information	Team Work
Time Management	Decision Making
Communication	Problem Solving
• Planner	Computer Aided Learning
Self Assisting	Setting Priorities
Multi Taking	Record Keeping

COMPUTER KNOWLEDGE

Operating Systems : Windows 98, 2000, XP, 2007

Software : MS Office, DTP,

Personal Information

Father's Name Jayeshbhai K Upadhyay

Date Of Birth 24th Oct 1982

Marital Status Married
Sex Male
Nationality Indian

Hobbies Reading, Cricket, Walking

REFERENCES

Professional Referee

Available on request